<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 4/2/2011 2:22:56 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!--Diplo Building Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCRIBE">
			<Text>School of Scribes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POSTOFFICE">
			<Text>Telephone Network</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--National Wonder Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUTENBERG_PRESS">
			<Text>Gutenberg Press</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOREIGN_OFFICE">
			<Text>Foreign Office</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- World Wonder Names -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORUM">
			<Text>Forum Romanum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUMMER_PALACE">
			<Text>Summer Palace</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARSAW_PACT">
			<Text>Warsaw Pact</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo Building Help-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCRIBE_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Diplomatic Units, +1 [ICON_SCIENCE] Science and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes connected to this city. Grants Promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Royal Signet[ENDCOLOR], which booss [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence earned by Diplomatic Units in the city in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POSTOFFICE_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Diplomatic Units, +2 [ICON_SCIENCE] Science and +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes connected to this city. Grants Promotion [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Wire Service[ENDCOLOR], which boosts [ICON_MOVES] movement for Diplomatic Units in the city in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo National Wonder Help-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUTENBERG_PRESS_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Diplomatic Units. All Diplomatic Units receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Literacy[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which boosts [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence earned, [ICON_MOVES] movement, and allows Diplomatic Units to ignore terrain costs.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a School of Scribes in all cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOREIGN_OFFICE_HELP">
			<Text>+50% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building Diplomatic Units. All Diplomatic Units receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Diplomatic Immunity[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which boosts [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence earned and allows Diplomatic Units to travel through rival territory without an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Open Borders[ENDCOLOR] agreement.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must have built a Telephone Network in all cities. The cost goes up the more cities there are in the empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo World Wonder Help-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORUM_HELP">
			<Text>+25% Diplomatic Unit Production and both land and sea trade routes produce an additional 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold when connecting to another civilization. All Diplomatic Units receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Imperial Seal[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which provides a boost to [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence earned from Diplomatic Missions and additional [ICON_MOVES] movement. Provides a free School of Scribes in the city in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUMMER_PALACE_HELP">
			<Text>+25% Diplomatic Unit Production in the city in which it is built. All Diplomatic Units receive the [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Nobility[ENDCOLOR] Promotion, which boosts [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence earned, provides additional [ICON_MOVES] movement, and allows Diplomatic Units to travel through rival territory without an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Open Borders[ENDCOLOR] agreement. Provides a free Garden in the city in which it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARSAW_PACT_HELP">
			<Text>Receive an immediate 30% [ICON_INFLUENCE] Influence boost with all City-States and +25% Diplomatic Unit Production in the city in which it is built. Provides a free Telephone Network in the city where it is built.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo Building Strategy-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SCRIBE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Increases [ICON_SCIENCE] Science output, [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes and Diplomatic Unit production speed and increases the amount of Influence received for Diplomatic Units built in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_POSTOFFICE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Increases [ICON_SCIENCE] Science output, [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_CONNECTED] Trade Routes and Diplomatic Unit production speed and the movement speed of Diplomatic Units built in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo National Wonder Strategy-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUTENBERG_PRESS_STRATEGY">
			<Text>This National Wonder cannot be built unless the civilization has a School of Scribes built in all of its cities. Build it to receive a +50% Diplomatic Unit Production bonus in the city where it is built, increased movement for all your Diplomatic Units and the ability to allow your Diplomatic Units to ignore terrain penalties.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FOREIGN_OFFICE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>This National Wonder cannot be built unless the civilization has a Telephone Network built in all of its cities. Build it to receive a +100% Diplomatic Unit Production bonus in the city where it is built, increased movement for all your Diplomatic Units and the ability to send your Diplomatic Units through rival territory without an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Open Borders[ENDCOLOR] agreement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Diplo World Wonder Strategy-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_FORUM_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build this world wonder to receive an early boost to your relations with nearby city-states through better-trained Diplomatic Units. Provides a free School of Scribes in the city in which it is built. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SUMMER_PALACE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build this wonder for your Diplomatic Units to be able to enter a rival's territory without an Open Borders agreement centuries before anyone else.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_WARSAW_PACT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Build this wonder to receive an enormous global influence boost with city-states you are currently allied to or at least friendly with (i.e. your influence with each city-state will increase by 50% of your current influence with said city-state).</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo Building Civilopedia Entries-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SCRIBE_TEXT">
			<Text>Long before the era of photocopiers or even the basic printing press, scribes were an essential aspect of the dissemination of knowledge. Copying religious texts, court documents and entire books by hand onto vellum (the skin of an animal) or papyrus, these individuals, often organized into guilds (or 'schools'), were essential to Ancient, Classical and Medieval communication.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_POSTOFFICE_TEXT">
			<Text>Though taken for granted today, the establishment of regional, national and eventually international telephone networks was a major boon to the economic, political and cultural interconnectivity of the world. By standardizing the speed and stability of communication on a global scale, modern telephone services are not only useful for spreading popular and intellectual knowledge, but also increased the rapidity of discourse between governments, most famously illustrated in the 20th century, during the Cold War, with the 'Red Phone Line' to Moscow on the desk of the President of the United States of America.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo National Wonder Entries-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_GUTENBERG_PRESS_TEXT">
			<Text>From a single print shop in Mainz, Germany, printing had spread to no less than around 270 cities in Central, Western and Eastern Europe by the end of the 15th century. As early as 1480, it is assumed that "the printed book was in universal use in Europe". By 1500, the printing presses in operation throughout Western Europe had already produced more than twenty million copies. European printing presses of around 1600 were capable of producing 3,600 impressions per workday. By comparison, movable type printing in the Far East, which did not know presses and was solely done by manually rubbing the back of the paper to the page, did not exceed an output of forty pages per day. The rapidity of typographical text production, as well as the sharp fall in unit costs, led to the issuing of the first newspapers which opened up an entirely new field for conveying up-to-date information to the public.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FOREIGN_OFFICE_TEXT">
			<Text>A Foreign Office was the heart of the Industrial Age empire. Teeming with vast, unending legions of civil servants, diplomats and assistants, all news both critical and mundane passed through the halls of the Foreign Office.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Diplo World Wonder Entries-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_FORUM_TEXT">
			<Text>The Roman Forum (Latin: Forum Romanum) is a rectangular forum (plaza) surrounded by the ruins of several important ancient government buildings at the center of the city of Rome. It was for centuries the center of Roman public life: the site of triumphal processions and elections, venue for public speeches, criminal trials, and gladiatorial matches, and nucleus of commercial affairs. The teeming heart of ancient Rome, it has been called the most celebrated meeting place in the world, and in all history.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_FORUM_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"I found Rome a city of bricks and left it a city of marble."[NEWLINE]- Augustus Caesar[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_SUMMER_PALACE_TEXT">
			<Text>Built in stages during the late-Medieval and Early Modern period, the Summer Palace was a large, splendid edifice to the power and might of the early Qing Dynasty and a counterpart to the Emperor's main palace in Beijing. Famous for its exsquisite landscaping, lush gardens and spectacular vista, the Summer Palace remains an important symbol of the power of Early Modern China and a popular tourist destination.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_SUMMER_PALACE_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"A monarchy is the most expensive of all forms of government...he who depends on his own power to rule, must strengthen that power by bribing the active and enterprising whom he cannot intimidate."[NEWLINE]- James F. Cooper[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_BUILDINGS_WARSAW_PACT_TEXT">
			<Text>The Warsaw Treaty Organization of Friendship, Cooperation, and Mutual Assistance (1955 to 1991), more commonly referred to as the Warsaw Pact, was a mutual defense treaty between eight communist states of Eastern Europe in existence during the Cold War. The founding treaty was established under the initiative of the Soviet Union and signed on 14 May 1955, in Warsaw. The Warsaw Pact was the military complement to the Council for Mutual Economic Assistance (COMECON), the regional economic organization for the communist states of Eastern Europe. The Warsaw Pact was a Soviet military response to the integration of West Germany into NATO in 1955, per the Paris Pacts of 1954.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_WONDER_WARSAW_PACT_QUOTE">
			<Text>[NEWLINE][TAB][TAB]"If any foreign minister begins to defend to the death a "peace conference," you can be sure his government has already placed its orders for new battleships and airplanes."[NEWLINE]- Joseph Stalin[NEWLINE][TAB]</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>