<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/6/2015 5:26:31 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARGON3_FORT">
			<Text>Walls of Sargon</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARGON3_FORT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Dur-Sharrukin ("Fortress of Sargon") was the Assyrian capital in the time of Sargon II of Assyria. The great city was entirely built in the decade preceding 706 BCE. After the unexpected death of Sargon in battle, the capital was shifted 20 km south to Nineveh.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Sargon II ruled from 722 to 705 BCE. In 717, Sargon ordered the construction of a new palace-city at the confluence of the Tigris and the Greater Zab rivers. The demands for timber and other materials and craftsmen, who came from as far as coastal Phoenicia, are documented in contemporary Assyrian letters. The debts of construction workers were nullified in order to attract a sufficient labour force. The land in the environs of the town was taken under cultivation, and olive groves were planted to increase Assyria's deficient oil-production. The great city was entirely built in the decade preceding 706 BCE, when the court moved to Dur-Sharrukin, although it was not completely finished yet. Sargon was killed during a battle in 705. After his unexpected death his son and successor Sennacherib abandoned the project, and relocated the capital with its administration to the city of Nineveh, 20 km south. The city was never completed and it was finally abandoned a century later when the Assyrian empire fell.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The city walls were massive and 157 towers protected its sides. A walled terrace contained temples and the royal palace.  The palace was adorned with sculptures and wall reliefs, and the gates were flanked with winged-bull shedu statues weighing up to 40 tons.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARGON3_FORT_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Walls of Sargon increase a city's Health and [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength, making the city more difficult to capture. They also yield a small amount of [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SARGON3_FORT_HELP">
			<Text>Defensive building of the Ancient Era that also yields a small amount of [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. Only Assyria may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>


	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SARGON3_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ASSYwalls256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SARGON3_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ASSYwalls128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SARGON3_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ASSYwalls64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SARGON3_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3ASSYwalls45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>

</GameData>