<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/6/2015 11:23:57 PM -->
<GameData>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3QURIKANCHA">
			<Text>Qurikancha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3QURIKANCHA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Qurikancha is an Incan unique building that increases the [ICON_PEACE] Faith of a city. Unlike the Temple it replaces, it also yields 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and has no maintenance cost.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3QURIKANCHA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Qurikancha (also called Inti Kancha or Inti Wasi), was the most important temple in the Inca Empire, dedicated primarily to Inti, the Sun God. It was one of the most revered temples of the capital city of Cusco. Pachacuti Inca Yupanqui rebuilt Cuzo and the House of the Sun, enriching it with more oracles and edifices, and adding plates of fine gold. He provided vases of gold and silver for the Mama-cunas, nuns, to use in the veneration services. Finally, he took the bodies of the seven deceased Incas, and enriched them with masks, head-dresses, medals, bracelets, sceptres of gold, placing them on a golden bench.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Spanish colonists built the Church of Santo Domingo on the site, demolishing the temple and using its foundations for the cathedral. Construction took most of a century. This is one of numerous sites where the Spanish incorporated Inca stonework into the structure of a colonial building. Major earthquakes severely damaged the church, but the Inca stone walls, built out of huge, tightly-interlocking blocks of stone, still stand due to their sophisticated stone masonry.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3QURIKANCHA_HELP">
			<Text>
				Increases the [ICON_PEACE] Faith and [ICON_GOLD] Gold of a city. Only the Incans may build it.

			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3QURIKANCHA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>Qurikancha256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3QURIKANCHA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>Qurikancha128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3QURIKANCHA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>Qurikancha64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3QURIKANCHA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>Qurikancha45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>

</GameData>