<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 1/17/2015 6:44:36 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_WAAG">
			<Text>Waag</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_WAAG_HELP">
			<Text>Renaissance Era building that yields [ICON_GOLD] and increases the amount of [ICON_GOLD] Gold from Trade Routes. Also reduces the rate at which enemy spies steal technology. Only the Netherlands may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_WAAG_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Waag is the Dutch unique building that increases the city's output of [ICON_GOLD] Gold. Trade routes other players make to a city with a Waag will generate an extra 2 [ICON_GOLD] to the trade route owner and an extra 3 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the city owner. In addition to yielding more [ICON_GOLD] Gold from trade routes than the Bank it replaces, the Waag also increases the time it takes for an enemy spy to steal your technology by 25%. The city must have a Market before the Waag may be constructed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_WAAG_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A weigh house or weighing house is a public building at or within which goods, and the like, are weighed. Most of these buildings were built before 1800, prior to the establishment of international standards for weights. As public control of the weight of goods was very important, they were run by local authorities who would also use them for the levying of taxes on goods transported through or sold within the city. Therefore, weigh houses would often be near a market square or town centre.
				Between 1550 and about 1690 people accused of witchcraft were at times brought to a weigh house in order to be subjected to a "witch test". If a person was found to be lighter than a set weight, he or she was deemed guilty. This is similar to the use of a ducking stool.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Weigh houses were especially common in the Netherlands, Germany, where they are called waag and waage respectively (both meaning "scale") and Poland (smatruz, in Krakow and Poznan). Outside the Netherlands and Germany the public weighing usually didn't take place in a special building, but in a town hall, guild hall, courthouse, or the like.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>WAAG_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>waag256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>WAAG_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>waag128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>WAAG_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>waag64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>WAAG_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>waag45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>