<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/6/2015 5:47:41 PM -->
<GameData>	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_TEXTILE">
			<Text>Textile Mill</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_TEXTILE_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Making cloth, by hand, for pants, shirts, socks, bedspreads and other domestic items had always required lots of skill and time. As population grew in England, more people needed and were willing to buy textile goods. The cottage industry showed how much people could produce in their homes through spinning and weaving cloth by hand, but this domestic production system could not keep up with the growing demands of England’s growing population. Instead, starting in the late 18th century, a series of innovations shifted textile production to a new factory system. As a result of the Industrial Revolution, cotton became the world’s most important non-food agricultural product-- and it remains so to this day.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]New inventions such as the Flying Shuttle and Spinning Jenny greatly increases the rate at which cotton was processed. Because the manufactoring was done by machine instead of by person, the machines could each work a full 24 hours without rest. Furthermore, the textile industry benefited from the assistance of the British Parliament, which subsequently outlawed the importation of superior cotton cloth from India.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_TEXTILE_HELP">
			<Text>Greatly increases the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of a city. Only England may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_TEXTILE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Textile Mill is an English unique building that greatly increases the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of a city. It has no resource requirement. Additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold from [ICON_RES_COTTON] Cotton, [ICON_RES_DYE] Dyes, and [ICON_RES_SILK] Silk resources.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>


	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_TEXTILE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_textile256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_TEXTILE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_textile128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_TEXTILE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_textile64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_TEXTILE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_textile45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>