<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 8/5/2013 2:12:16 PM -->
<GameData>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_MISSION">
			<Text>Mission</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_HELP">
			<Text>Increases the rate at which [ICON_GREAT_PERSON] Great People are born and increases religious pressure emanating from the city. Only Spain can build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Mission is a Spanish unique building that increases the rate at which [ICON_GREAT_PERSON] Great People are born in the city. Unlike the Garden it replaces, it does not require Fresh Water and increases religious pressure emanating from this city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Spanish missions in the Americas were Christian missions established by the Spanish Empire during the 15th to 19th centuries in an area extending from Mexico and the southwestern portions of what today are the United States, southwards as far as Argentina and Chile. The Catholic Church inaugurated a major effort to spread Christianity in the New World by converting indigenous peoples. As such, the establishment of Christian missions went hand-in-hand with the colonizing efforts of European powers such as Spain, France and Portugal. For these nations, "the colonial enterprise was based on the necessity to develop European commerce and the obligation to propagate the Christian faith.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Over the course of the mission period Indian population levels declined rapidly and substantially, plummeting well over 90 percent in many areas. Depopulation, combined with widespread forced resettlements dating to 1656 and 1657, eventually led to the abandonment of Georgia's interior missions. Beginning with a devastating 1661 raid on the Santo Domingo de Talaje Mission at the mouth of the Altamaha River, there were also armed slave-raids by Indians allied with the English. These raids finally resulted in the retreat of all coastal missions to the barrier islands by 1685.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_mission256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_mission128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_mission64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>BUILDING_4UC_MISSION_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_mission45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>