<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 7/29/2013 3:00:44 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_OPERA_HOUSE">
				<Text>Orchestra</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_OPERA_HOUSE_HELP">
			<Text>Greatly increases the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture of a city. Only Austria may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_OPERA_HOUSE_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Orchestra is an Austrian unique building that increases the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture of a city, moreso than the Opera House it replaces. Requires an Amphitheater in the city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_4UC_OPERA_HOUSE_TEXT">
			<Text>An orchestra is a large instrumental ensemble that contains sections of string, brass, woodwind, and percussion instruments. Other instruments such as the piano and celesta may sometimes be grouped into a fifth section such as a keyboard section or may stand alone, as may the concert harp and electric and electronic instruments. The orchestra grew by accretion throughout the 18th and 19th centuries, but changed very little in composition during the course of the 20th century.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Vienna has long been an important centre of musical innovation. Composers of the 18th and 19th centuries were drawn to the city by the patronage of the Habsburgs, and made Vienna the European capital of classical music. Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, Ludwig van Beethoven, and Johann Strauss, Jr., among others, were associated with the city. Vienna's status began its rise as a cultural center in the early 16th century, and was focused around instruments including the lute. The Vienna Philharmonic, founded in 1842, is regularly considered one of the finest orchestras in the world.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>


	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AUSTRIA_OPERA_HOUSE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>philharm256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AUSTRIA_OPERA_HOUSE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>philharm128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AUSTRIA_OPERA_HOUSE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>philharm64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AUSTRIA_OPERA_HOUSE_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>philharm45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>