<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 10/9/2013 7:54:56 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH">
			<Text>Monolithic Church</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_HELP">
			<Text>				
				Increases [ICON_PEACE] Faith and bolsters religious pressure emanating from this City. Only Ethiopia may build it.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Monlithic Church is an Ethiopian unique building, that increases the [ICON_PEACE] Faith generated by a city. Unlike the Temple it replaces, it also yields +1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith from [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone tiles and increases religious pressure emanating from this City. City must already have a Shrine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The term "monolithic church" (or "rock-hewn church") is most often used to refer to the complex of 11 churches in Lalibela, Ethiopia, believed to have been created in the 12th century. The medieval monolithic churches of this 12th-century 'New Jerusalem' are situated in a mountainous region in the heart of Ethiopia near a traditional village. Lalibela is an important center of Ethiopian Christianity, and even today is a place of pilgrimage and devotion. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Many other churches were hewn from rock in Ethiopia, outside of Lalibela. This practice was very common in Tigray, where the outside world knew of only a few such churches until the Catholic priest Abba Tewelde Medhin Josief presented a paper to the Third International Conference of Ethiopian Studies in which he announced the existence of over 120 churches, 90 of which were still in use. Research over the next few years raised the total number of these rock-hewn churches to 153.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>Lalibela_Icon256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>Lalibela_Icon128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>Lalibela_Icon064.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>MONOLITHIC_CHURCH_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>Lalibela_Icon045.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>