<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 7/29/2013 8:39:43 PM -->
<GameData>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_AGORA">
			<Text>Agora</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_AGORA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Agora is a Greek unique building that increases the amount of [ICON_GOLD] Gold a city generates, moreso than the Market it replaces. Trade routes other players make to a city with an Agora will generate an extra 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the city owner and the trade route owner gains an additional 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold for the trade route.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_AGORA_HELP">
			<Text>Yields [ICON_GOLD] Gold and increases the amount of [ICON_GOLD] Gold a city generates from Trade routes. Only Greece may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_AGORA_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The agora was a central spot in ancient Greek city-states, and the center of political and public life in Athens. Early in Greek history, free-born male land-owners who were citizens would gather in the agora for military duty or to hear statements of the ruling king or council. Later, the agora also served as a marketplace where merchants kept stalls or shops to sell their goods amid colonnades. From this twin function of the agora as a political and commercial space came the two Greek verbs agorázō (I shop) and agoreúō (I speak in public).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Forum was the Roman equivalent of the agora and the word is often used in older texts to refer to Greek agoras. The pattern of the agora is still present in the vast majority of all Mediterranean social and urban structures. This main square tends to be heavily used all year round. This in contrast with, for example, colder places in Europe due to weather conditions.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AGORA_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>greek_agora256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AGORA_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>greek_agora128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AGORA_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>greek_agora64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>AGORA_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>greek_agora45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>